Downloaded @ subs4free.club
Everything looks so beautiful from up here.
I'll say.
I've been thinking about you all week.
I can't get you out of my mind.
I've been thinking about you, too.
God, you're amazing.
You know that?
What's wrong?
It's just you deserve more than this.
This moment right here, this is all I need.
Tom.
I'm sorry. I can't.
It's okay. It's okay.
Emma, you've gotta talk to me.
This isn't gonna work.
We can't do this anymore.
Listen...
I know this is not
how we expected things to go.
But I really care about you.
You can't say you don't feel
the same way about me.
How I feel doesn't matter.
Emma.
Emma, wait.
Just meet with me tomorrow.
I don't want this
to be the last time I see you.
- We can't.
- Why?
Because it's my anniversary.
I'm sorry. It's over.
Mark Webster's office, please hold.
Happy anniversary, Mrs. Webster.
Oh, they're beautiful. Thank you.
Thanks for waiting. How can I help you?
No, I've already stated
that we have no comment.
Stop it!
Thanks, Selena.
Hello, pumpkin.
I thought you were gonna wear the red dress.
You know that's my favorite.
I know. I just thought that maybe
we could try something a little different.
It's okay.
There's still time to stop
by the apartment and change.
What's that?
Nothing.
Emma, you know that's only
going to trigger your anxiety.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing with my file?
They're revoking his parole.
Don't you wish you were
still putting guys like that in jail
instead of keeping them out?
I don't miss living out
of a shoebox in Birmingham
wearing cheap suits,
and I don't miss doing
everyone else's dirty work.
Up here everyone else
does the dirty work for me.
Do you know what I do miss, though?
I miss that carefree girl.
One of the few photos I have of you
in front of the camera.
What was she thinking?
I don't remember.
Oh, sir.
Pardon me.
You've met my wife, haven't you?
I don't think so.
Emma, this is Tom Gorman.
We met at the Christmas party
last year, actually.
That's right. You auctioned off some of your
photographs you took for charity.
- They were stunning.
- No, no.
You both know it wasn't the Christmas party.
It was the holiday party,
lest we offend the PC police.
Much on for the weekend?
Just paperwork,
somebody's gotta keep the...
Emma, darling.
Yes?
- I drove.
- Right.
Nice to meet you again.
Monday.
Now, that was delicious.
Would you like some dessert?
- I'm fine. Thank you.
- How is the gateau a la creme?
- It's to die for.
- Perfect.
We'll take two.
Of course.
I thought we weren't doing gifts.
I wanted to surprise you tonight.
They say diamonds are a girl's best friend,
but 11 years apparently
makes it our steel anniversary,
so I had this specially made.
It's beautiful.
Thank you.
- Try it on.
- Oh, my gosh!
Yay!
That was you not so long ago.
Hey.
You still with us?
Yeah.
I thought we weren't doing gifts.
Super Bowl?
Fifty yard line, you did always say
that you wanted to go, and I thought
that maybe this year
the Steelers would be in it.
Not a chance.
They suck this year.
They're, like, 4-12.
Let me.
Happy anniversary, pumpkin.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
I know it is none of my business,
and I know that you feel like you just made
a huge commitment out there,
but I just want you to understand
that nothing is set in stone.
Yeah, you're right.
It's none of your business.
No, I... I know, you're right.
I'm sorry.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Before we head on home,
there's one final surprise, babe.
Check your pockets.
Can you please just tell me
where we're going?
No.
We're almost there, I promise.
You've been saying that for an hour.
Yeah, but this time I mean it.
Just try and have some fun,
would you? Come on.
Being blindfolded for over an hour
really isn't my idea of fun.
It was when we first got married.
I'm not... I'm not doing this.
I can't do it. I feel carsick.
I'm taking it off. I don't...
Stop.
You're gonna ruin the surprise.
Mark, I really don't know
what kind of weird game you're playing,
but I don't want to fool around.
Mark.
Mark. Mark, where are we going?
The lake house?
Surprise. I had them prepare it
for us today.
It's so strange in the winter.
We have a lot of happy memories here.
I thought maybe
we can rekindle some of them.
75, 76,
77, 78, 79...
Fuck it.
"I love you with all my heart.
Till death do us part."
♪ Lies with every eye ♪
♪ Sitting on my nose ♪
♪ Flowers on the wall ♪
♪ Keep growing high ♪
♪ Realizing no time ♪
♪ No time left at all ♪
♪ A falling leaf am I ♪
♪ A falling leaf ♪
♪ Am I ♪
♪ Let him in all upon ♪
♪ Showing no life at all ♪
♪ Missing water and heat and ground ♪
♪ And looking to the sky ♪
♪ Grim reaper comes ♪
♪ Hoping grass was tall ♪
♪ Wind, please help me ♪
♪ A falling leaf ♪
Took you long enough.
You know, it's really not fair.
What?
That you just get
more beautiful as you get older.
Well, I started out very ugly.
Mm.
Emma, I know
that things have been bad between us,
been bad for a while,
and I'm sorry.
You've been through so much,
and I haven't been a good husband.
I know one stupid anniversary surprise
isn't gonna fix everything,
but it's a start.
We owe it that much, don't we?
♪ Laying here in pieces ♪
♪ Day's work all been done ♪
♪ Guess I got what man receives ♪
♪ On plain reality ♪
♪ But wait my knees are falling ♪
♪ Falling everywhere ♪
♪ Are we not all falling leaves? ♪
♪ Are we not all ♪
♪ Falling leaves ♪
Oh, my God. It's freezing.
Morning, sweetheart.
How are you feeling?
Hungover.
Mm.
Did you dream beautiful things?
Ah...
What the fuck is this?
What is this?
Mark? Mark?
It's time to wake up.
Oh, shit!
Help!
Please.
Oh, come on. Come on.
Please help me, please, please.
Yes!
No, no. No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no! Fuck!
Keys. Fuck yes!
Oh.
Thought you would be lighter
without all that blood.
Oh. Okay. Oh, come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
Yes!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Fuck.
Oh, motherfucker.
- Why?
- ♪ It's so very hard to find ♪
♪ To need someone to love ♪
Our wedding tune.
Remember?
I have to admit.
I'm impressed you made it this far.
You should have knelt at my feet
after everything I did for you.
When I met you, you were nothing...
a failed photographer
with no money, no hope.
My only regret is not being there
to see the look on your face right now.
I don't want to give you
the satisfaction of thinking
I put a bullet in my head
because of your disobedience,
but I was being called away,
and I couldn't just sit back and watch you
live happily ever after, with him.
Happy anniversary, pumpkin.
♪ Need somebody ♪
♪ At least that's what some people say ♪
No.
No, fuck.
Ah.
Ohh!
No!
Oh.
Okay. Okay.
Fuck.
You can do this.
I can do this.
Ah!
Ow.
You fucking hypocrite!
How many fucking times
did I wash lipstick and glitter
off of your fucking shirts?
I was dragging around
that lifeless corpse of yours
long before you put a bullet
in that deranged head of yours.
You just didn't know it yet.
Ahh.
I'm gonna cut myself free of you,
if it's the last thing I do.
Oh.
Ow.
It's 11:26 a.m. July 2nd.
I'm the assistant district attorney,
and we'll be personally
overseeing your case.
I know you're weak and tired,
but we need you to tell us
everything about the attack last night.
He came out of the shadows, and he...
he ripped the camera out of my hands.
I made a... a run for it.
I tried to run, and then that's
when I felt, um...
the... the knife.
I-I went to scream for help but...
It's okay.
The detective mentioned
you mutilated your attacker.
My keys... um, I had...
I had my keys clenched in my fist, and...
That's the last thing that I remember.
Hey, you're safe now. You're safe.
I've got this. We've apprehended...
Fuck!
- No!
- Ahh!
Ohh.
- Ah.
- Tom?
You broke my nose.
What are you doing here?
You gotta be kidding me, right?
Does, "I fucked up,
and I need your help" ring a bell?
- What?
- The message you sent me.
Tom, I didn't send you a message.
Do you have any idea the shitstorm
your husband's caused back at the office?
Is that blood on your shirt?
Oh, Tom, Mark sent you those messages.
Is he here?
Most of him.
What do you mean?
Jesus fucking Christ.
Mark shot himself.
He what? What the fuck happened?
He handcuffed himself to me,
and then he shot himself in the head.
Is it because of us?
I'm pretty sure it was
because he was insane.
Okay.
If you... Should we cover his...
His what?
I'm sorry. I haven't seen
my boss in his boxers before.
I'm freaking out a little bit.
- You're freaked out?
- Why would he do this?
- Shit, the raid.
- The what?
Last night the DA raided his entire office.
They placed charges against Mark...
evidence of tampering on multiple cases.
This is why I tried to call you.
So this fuckstain knew his entire career
was going down the drain,
and so he's just trying to drag me down too.
Fuck.
- You call the police?
- He trashed my phone.
Okay. We got time to get our story straight.
What story? He killed himself.
You washed your face?
Yeah, I rinsed my dead husband's
blood and brains off. Why?
Do you think that I did this?
Of course not, but the cop
is gonna ask you that question.
Okay, so let a cop ask that question.
I'll tell him the fucking truth.
You gotta understand, the truth is not
necessarily your best friend right now.
Trust me, I do this for a living.
So what do I do? I lie to the police.
No. We manage the truth.
This doesn't look good for either of us.
I don't give a shit
about looking good right now.
Well, you gave a shit five minutes ago
when you washed the evidence off your face.
- Call the fucking police.
- Listen.
Have you stopped to think about why
Mark sent you that message?
Because I woke up handcuffed
to my dead husband
whose carcass I've been dragging
around the entire house.
He siphoned all of the gas out of the car.
He thought to remove every sharp object.
I have been chained to
this nightmare all day.
Do you really think that
he sent you that text
so you could come here
and you could save me?
Call the police!
Okay. You're right.
Shit.
I left it on charge.
Do you recognize that car?
No.
Passed him about a mile back.
He was parked up on the side of the road.
Tom, we have to run.
How do you expect to do that?
Listen, okay let me handle this.
No. You can't go out there.
The only thing this guys knows for sure
is that I'm here, that's it.
You lock the door, and don't open it
for anybody else that's not me. Okay?
- No, no, no, no.
- Don't open it
- for anybody who's not me.
- No, no, Tom.
- Shit.
- Lock the door.
Shit.
Tom, be careful.
- Can I help you?
- Yeah, I sure hope so.
Are you the owner of the property?
No. Gotta come back another time.
Yeah, see, a Mr. Webster.
hired us to fix a burst pipe, you know?
Said he'd be here today to let us inside.
Well, like I said no one's here, so...
How much did he say
he was going to pay you?
I'll cover it, and you can be on your way.
Do you mind if we settle inside?
It's cold as a witch's tit out here,
you know?
Actually I do.
How much?
I, uh...
We agreed upon an even 200.
Here's 50 on top.
Ain't you a gentleman?
Drive safe.
Actually, uh,
Mind if I use your facilities?
I just drove all the way from Buffalo,
and I'm about ready to burst, you know?
It's out of order.
Out of order?
Listen, you got a problem
with me or something?
You said you drove from Buffalo,
over 250 miles just to fix a burst pipe?
With Indiana plates?
I gave you what you came for,
and still you're standing here,
so yeah, I got a problem
with you or something.
I think you should leave.
Listen, why don't you just let us inside
so we can do our job, all right?
Look, fuck off, now!
All right. All right.
We don't have to do this,
all right, we could just...
I've already notified the police.
- Just walk away.
- I suggest you get back in your car.
Please, please, Bob...
Shit!
Holy shit.
Jesus, Bobby.
You killed him. You fuckin' killed him.
You fuck... I'm so sorry. I'm sorry, man.
Hey, hey, careful.
They got your prints on file.
- He's already called the cops.
- No because if he did,
we would have heard it over the scanner.
Oh, shit. Bobby, we're fucked, man.
Oh, my God. I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
What are we doing, Bob?
What are you fucking doing?
You just fuckin' relax.
What are we doing here, Bobby?
Bobby, we gotta go. We gotta go.
- Jimmy, Jimmy, Jimmy.
- Look at this shit.
- No.
Calm down. Calm down.
Hey, shh, listen. It's fine.
- It's fine.
- You said...
you said you were gonna tie him up.
You said nothing about killing a man.
I know, and I'm sorry, okay,
but listen little brother,
I need you to focus right now.
Okay. We need to find her still. All right?
Don't leave me.
What are you going to do when you find her?
Listen, you just yell out if you spot her.
Jimmy, okay?
Oh.
Ah!
Jesus fucking Christ!
Bobby, Bobby!
It's over there.
What's wrong?
Hey, careful, the ice could be thin.
God.
Looks like the wolves got to him.
You ever seen a wolf use an anchor?
Aw, fuck. It's him.
- Who?
- The guy who hired us. Fuck.
That's the guy that hired us?
The lawyer that put you away?
Yeah, we found common ground.
Bobby, what the fuck
are we still doing here then?
We're not leaving until we open that safe.
Well, then let's go.
Let's go and do it
and leave this girl behind.
Huh? Lawyer dude's fucking dead, huh?
- Contract's null and dead.
- You don't understand.
There were two people who knew
the combination to that safe.
And one of them is now
missing part of his head.
Just give me a second to think.
She could be miles away by now.
Not without shoes.
Bobby!
Yeah?
This is some pretty high tech shit.
Any chance of blowing it open?
Not without turning
everything inside into dust.
Shit.
Yeah, and that's not the worst of it.
See this model?
Well, it needs a combination
and a fingerprint.
- Hers?
- Maybe.
I mean, it would have to be programmed in,
so I'd put my money on him.
There's only one way to find out.
I mean, what do I look like
the fucking undertaker?
In and out, you said.
We open the safe, and we split the diamonds.
All right. I'll get the body.
You find the girl.
Fuck you, man.
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
Fuckin' hell.
20 fuckin' minutes.
I'm out here freezing my nuts off.
Why don't you get the fuckin' body?
Ohh.
Oh, God.
Shit.
- What did you do?
- Nothing. It wasn't me.
Can you switch it off?
20 minutes, in and out.
That's what you said.
Bobby. Bobby. Bobby, Bobby.
Just listen to me, okay?
She's already put you
behind bars once before.
Don't make the same mistake again.
The only mistake I made
was leaving her still breathing.
She could be anywhere by now. It's over.
- No, it's not.
- It's over.
It's not.
- Ten years I spent...
- No. Get off me.
Please. Look at me.
Ten years I spent inside that cage,
ten fucking years,
while they repossessed our house,
the house that we grew up in,
while Pop got sick.
This bitch took everything from us, Jimmy,
and those diamonds
are compensation for that.
Okay? And we are still in the game.
How do you think she triggered
the car alarm?
- The keys.
- Why?
Because we were right next to her.
Yes. She wanted to distract us
because she's still in the house, okay?
We got this. You take the back,
I'll take the front, okay?
- Yeah, all right.
- Good boy.
Go on. You're good.
Bobby.
Bobby? Bobby.
Bobby. Holy shit.
Bobby. Bobby, what the hell happened? Huh?
Ah! Ah, ah.
No, no, no, no.
No! Bobby! Bobby, get up!
Ah!
No. No, no, stop, please.
Don't...
Fucker.
911, what's the emergency?
- Help!
- Ma'am?
Ma'am, can you hear me?
- She called the cops?
- Yeah, she tried to.
Shit!
We gotta get out of here. Jimmy.
Listen, the cops are gonna trace the call.
We're in the middle of nowhere, okay.
We still have time.
Bobby. Bobby, listen. Listen.
No, we're not leaving here until we're done.
Well, then I'm telling you
I'm done. All right?
Listen to me, you ungrateful little prick.
We are five fucking minutes
away from 200 grand in rocks.
All right? So you drag
that corpse up those stairs
or you fucking become one.
Do you understand me?
- Ah!
- Yeah, yeah. Now, fucking go!
I don't know the combination.
We'll see about that.
Emma? Emma? It's a beautiful thing.
Time to wake up.
Wake up.
Ah! Ow.
Ah.
Figured you'd want to spend
your last precious moments
with the old ball and chain.
Such a perfect couple.
I already told you that I don't know
the combination to the safe.
No.
Bobby. Bobby, we don't need to do this.
- No. No, no, no, no, no, no!
- Stay down! Stay there!
There it is. My shadow.
Half my world went dark that night,
but there's a light
on the other side of that door,
and the combination according to your husband
is the day that he proposed to you.
Okay, what do you expect me to do?
Just give you the date so you
can kill me right afterwards?
- I expect you to scream.
- Uh!
No, no, no, no, no, no. Please stop.
We'll see how quiet you stay
with no fucking toes.
- Bobby.
- Help me!
- Stop, Bobby.
- Okay. No.
Don't you fuckin' move.
- Stay there.
- Ah, oh!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, please, please.
Jimmy, what are you doing?
No one else needs to get hurt.
- Gimme the gun.
- No.
- Gimme the gun now.
- Fuck you!
Fuck me?
Fuck you, you sicken me.
Go stand by the safe.
Leave the knife.
Man, I swear...
Fuck.
Okay.
Come on, what the fuck are you
gonna do then?
Okay. Here's what's gonna happen.
All right. You give us the combination,
we take the diamonds and leave you here alive.
Jesus Christ,
what do you think she's gonna do?
The moment she's outta here,
she's gonna go straight to the cops.
Shut up! Fuck!
Who do you think is the first person
the cops are going to come looking for
when they find her dead body, huh?
You already put a target
on our backs, you dumb fuck.
We should never have come here.
I'll give it to you,
but you gotta fuckin' cut me loose.
- Combination first.
- Fuck that.
Not as long as I'm attached
to this fuckin' piece of shit.
Jimmy, we don't have fucking time.
Just let me cut the date out of her,
and we're done.
I pick open those handcuffs
and you give me the combination,
but no one is leaving
until that safe is open.
All right? Okay?
- Fine.
- Okay, but let's hurry it
the fuck along then, shall we?
Come on, Jimmy. Let's go.
Here, Just gimme the handcuffs.
Okay. Let's have that date.
July 29th, 2011.
What the fuck?
What?
"The diamonds you seek
lay close to her heart."
The necklace.
The diamonds are in the necklace.
It doesn't open. It doesn't come off.
Let me try. Where's the clasp?
There isn't one.
This fucker made it so it won't open.
All right.
Jesus, what's this thing made of?
He doesn't want us to cut
the necklace off her.
He wants us to cut her off the necklace.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, I got this. I got this.
Get it off. Get it off. Please.
I can break this off. I can break this off.
Shit.
Hold it out.
No, no, please.
Jimmy, get out of the fuckin' way.
No, no, no, please, just let me have a go.
Let me cut it.
Ah!
No. Bobby, Bobby!
I'm not gonna let you do this!
I'm not losing you again!
Jimmy, stop. Get off me!
God dammit, Jimmy!
- Stop it.
- Get off me!
No, no, no.
Oh.
This is all your fault.
You fuckin' did this.
I'm gonna cut your fuckin' head off.
Fuck you.
Ah!
Fucking bitch!
Ow! Ohh!
Oh, God.
Please, please, please.
Ah!
Ohh.
Fuck.
Ohh!
Fuck you!
Shit.
♪ Sometimes I wonder ♪
Fuck!
There's nowhere to run, you bitch!
Ahh!
You fucking bitch!
Ah!
Ahh!